♪ ♪
Huh.
You know. it's good to
be outside. you know?
Like. outdoors and stuff.
This is God's country.
Yeah.
Let's get some bottles
and break them in
the parking lot.
Yeah. back to nature.
Uh...
what the hell is going on here?
What did they do to
this place. Butt-Head?
What's going on?
- Beavis and Butt-Head...
what a pleasant surprise
to see you guys here.
What happened to
the parking lot?
What did you do?
Well. once a month. we have
a farmers' market here.
and it turns into a cornucopia
of locally sourced
farm-to-table cuisine.
Does "cornucopia" mean butthole?
It sure does. Beavis.
What it means is we
have a bountiful harvest
of produce and crafts.
- Damn it.
- Uh...
well. we just came
here to break stuff.
so we'll just have
some of those jars.
Oh. well. that's honey.
My lady friend Ellen is a
beekeeper and makes her own.
That'll be $50.
- Whoa. $50?
- Whoa.
And you made that?
Oh. well. the bees made it.
I just reap the benefits.
It's great if you have allergies
or Fibromyalgia.
- Beavis...
we gotta get some bees.
- Why's that?
- Because. dumbass.
we're gonna get rich and make
a bunch of dumb bugs
do all the work.
Oh. yeah. yeah.
Yeah. work sucks.
Let's go find a beehive. Beavis.
Yeah.
I saw a beehive
over here somewhere.
Hey. boys. be
careful 'round here.
There's a big old wasp
nest on my property.
I'm gonna call an exterminator.
but I don't want to hear
what they're gonna charge me.
I tell you what.
- What's he saying?
- It's just no expense...
- Uh. I don't know.
Probably just a
bunch of old stuff.
There it is. Beavis.
When I look at that.
I see fat stacks of cash.
Yeah. this is gonna be cool.
It's too high. Butt-Head.
Try knocking it down
with this big fork thing.
Okay.
Watch what you're
doing. asswipe.
- Yeah. sorry.
- Ow!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
That was cool.
Wake up. Beavis.
I got the bees.
Whoa. cool.
We're gonna be rich. yeah.
This is gonna be cool.
♪ 'Cause I'm in
the stars tonight ♪
Yes! This song kicks ass.
Yeah.
Yeah. the video kicks ass. too.
♪ Shoes on. get
up in the morn' ♪
Uh. what?
What did you just say?
Oh. I said...
I didn't say anything.
Uh. I thought I heard
you say this kicks ass.
Did you say that. Beavis?
No. no. I was talking
about something else.
Don't lie to me. Beavis.
I heard you loud and clear.
No. no.  I was just
joking. Butt-Head.
I was just. you know...
You know. saying.
"Yeah. this kicks ass."
you know. but. you know...
But it sucks. you know?
I was just being. like. iconic
or. like... you know
who sucks the worst?
It's J-Hope. yeah.
He doesn't even have
the positive attitude.
you know. like Suga.
You know their names?
What the hell has
gotten into you. Beavis?
I was kidding. Butt-Head.
I don't like these guys.
I just said they suck.
You know. I just. um...
I just know their
names 'cause. you know.
'cause I hate them
so much. that's all.
Beavis. I'm going to leave now.
I'm gonna leave
you with your. uh.
seven or eight. or 15.
BTS boy band dudes.
Come on. Butt-Head.
I just wasn't paying
attention or something.
Come on.
♪ Bring the fire and
set the night alight ♪
Comin' up like rock and roll.
You know. Beavis.
I'm not mad. I'm
just disappointed.
Jesus Christ. Beavis.
- Come on. Butt-Head.
I was just. um...
- What the hell
is going on in here?
- I was just thinking
about something else.
Beavis. I wish I
had walked in here
and you were taking
a dump on the couch
or doing homework.
Anything would be
better than that.
Okay. okay. I mean...
Beavis. I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
I think this is
my house. though.
- Not anymore. Beavis.
- Okay.
I'll just come back later.
No. never come back.
Bunghole.
♪ ♪
Um. so it's been. like.
two hours or something.
You think the bees
are done making honey?
Uh. I don't know.
Uh. doesn't sound like
there's honey in there.
Stupid bugs.
Beavis. we need to teach
these bees a lesson.
Make honey. you dumbass bugs.
Yeah. really.
It's like. all you do is
just sit there in that box.
Aah. you just sit there!
Aah.
Maybe your mother
puts up with it.
but I don't. Aah!
You're in my house now. Aah.
That means my rules.
- Settle down. Beavis.
- Son of a bitch!
Whoa. You hear that?
That's the sound of money.
What'd you say. Butt-Head?
I said. "That's the
sound of money"!
Oh. yeah. yeah.
Yeah. yeah. money
kicks ass. Yeah.
Okay. Beavis.
Now open the box
and grab the honey.
Uh. Butt-Head. I
kind of don't want to
because. um. I don't
want to get stung again.
It hurts.
Don't be a wuss.
Besides. we got.
like. protective gear.
So this will. like.
protect me from the bees?
- Yep.
- Okay.
- Get that honey. Beavis.
- Here we go. yeah.
Aah! No!
Aaaah!
Beavis. you look silly.
Aah! Aah. no!
Aah! Ow.
Stop. ow. Stop. stop. ow. ow.
Whoa. look at all
the honey. Beavis.
We're gonna be rich.
Uh. so. like. honey for sale.
Fresh honey! It's
really expensive.
That's right.
It's. like. $1.000.
Buy it right now for money.
Beavis and Butt-Head.
Boys. are you feeling okay?
Buy our honey. Our
bees made it. yeah.
Check it out.
- That's right.
It's expensive.
Fresh from the bug's butt.
This tastes like
shampoo. mm-kay?
What? Our bees made shampoo?
These dumb bugs made
the wrong stuff.
Guys. these are not
bees. They're wasps.
Wasps don't make honey.
We know. dumbass.
They made shampoo.
Yeah. yeah.
So are you gonna buy
our shampoo or not?
No. thank you.
I buy artisanal lavender shampoo
over at booth 12.
These bees suck.
They made crappy shampoo
nobody wants to buy.
Since we got this free shampoo.
I'm gonna go.
like. wash my hair.
Just open this up here...
What?
Damn it. now those dumb bugs
made fruit or something.
Aah. damn it.
Now. you just relax.
While you were
selling your honey.
I bought everything
I need to make
my special summer
squash vegan bisque.
Aw. David. that sounds so...
Oh. my! Oh. no!
Aaaah!
Ow!
Aah!
Oh. my God! Get off!
♪ ♪
Chirp.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today